and who would they like? It’s better to be a
а кем бы хотели Лучше быть там
dentist or a
стоматологом или
deputy there. Well, probably a deputy, yes, or a
депутатом Ну депутатом наверно да ну или
deputy’s wife, no, a deputy, a deputy. How will you
депутата нет депутату депутату А как ты
become a deputy yourself? What’s wrong with that?
сама станешь депутатом А что
Hello girls, something
такого Здравствуйте девчонки что-то нас
switched us over, then I already know that’s how I play it. It
переключила тогда я аж я знаете так
happens that we didn’t agree  do
ИТ Бывает такое мы не договорили есть у
you have any questions ask
вас какие-то вопросы спрашивайте вот
just now when it was better to talk to you again
только что кая это снова была лучше с
Burn
поговорить Горите
Say damn what question did you become a
Говорите блин какой вопрос Вы с стали
deputy how and how did you become a deputy bought a
депутатом как а как стал депутатом купил
place on the list there yes bought a place on the
место в списке там да купил место в
list And they’ve already passed Well there was
списке А там уже прошли Ну там была
the party is promoted,
партия раскрученный
of course, but we would probably have to buy a
конечно так а нам бы пришлось покупать
place. No, look. Either you
же наверное место Не ну смотрите Либо вы
can buy it yourself or you may have a
сами можете купить либо у вас может быть
friend, let’s call it a deputy who will
друг так назовём депутат который себе
buy it for you. Well, not two at once, but
купит И вам Ну не двум сразу а кому-то
you bought it for someone else,
одному вы купил
let’s be like one  a person has two
давайте мы будем как один человек две
heads. Well, let’s say I would buy someone
головы Ну скажем так я бы купил кому-то
one, but two at once. No, that’s kind of
одну но двух сразу Нет это ну как бы
the point: you’re buying one place, but we
смысл вы покупаете одно место но у нас
’ll have two heads. So don’t let them in, look,
будет две головы Так не пускать смотри
you know, but two two deputies
понимаешь а двух двух депутатов мне
will be unprofitable for me because look, I’m
будет невыгодно потому что смотри я
investing like this  you will get into the Council of such a
инвестирую так вы пройдёте в Совет так
city Well, I’ll sit next to one
городской Ну с одной я буду рядом сидеть
and the second will be there all the time I won’t have
а вторая будет постоянно у меня не будет
that much time with her Well pay
времени с ней столько Ну уделять
attention She’ll find another
внимание Она найдёт себе другого
deputy Well somehow why should I
депутата Ну как-то зачем мне тогда
invest money then True Well yes yes
инвестировать бабки Правда Ну да да Вот
That’s right  so, like, well, one
то есть а так типа ну одну
could be so, well, you see,
можно было бы так что вот Ну понимаешь
this is also like just an investment,
это тоже такое как бы просто инвестиция
it should get
она должна получить
a return, you know what
отдачу понимаете о чём
I mean, and the World Cup is all Well, at least not Hearing knocks out the
я а ЧМ всё Ну хотя бы не Слыш выбивает
sound Well, what is your income, you
звук Ну в чём ваш заработок состоит вы
said Not quite right, let’s say so  not
сказали Не совсем лега скажем так не
also legal, it’s like I don’t decide the
тоже легальны его как бы не решаю
solutions are different. So for example, well, for
решения разные Так например вот ну для
some people who are also engaged in
каких-то людей которые занимаются тоже
certain types of activities,
определёнными видами деятельности так
so they need a solution Yes, and we decide, they kind of
вот им нужно решение Да и решаем они как
thank me for the Solution, well, it’s like there’s
бы благодарят меня за Решение вот ну как
something to eat for  what to
бы есть за что покушать есть за что
refuel the machine Well, as you understand We are not
заправить машинку Ну как вы понимаете Не
complaining So I will say And who are you studying for?
жалуемся Так что и я скажу А вы на кого
By the way, we are doctors doto what
Кстати а мы это докторы дото на какой
specialization is dentistry stomato oh
специализации стоматология стомато о
dentists are also very popular
тоже сейчас очень популярны стоматологи
now, I went now We have an
сейчас вот я ходил У нас есть там
elite salon there like this Oh well I  I’ll say this, the
элитный салончик такой О ну я скажу так
dentist now has good dentistry,
стоматолог сейчас хорошая стоматология
it’s not cheap, even for me, as a deputy,
это недёшево даже мне как депутату там
we have specialists there, uh Well, everything is so clear with them,
есть у нас спец такие ээ Ну у них так
it used to be that there’s a dentist, you
всё чётко это раньше там стоматолог
come there when you’re a child, they keep you there, they
приходишь тебя там в детстве держат
drill you, and now please, the
сверлят А сейчас пожалуйста такие
girls are so neat, they
аккуратненький девочки они там
serve there, the boy is also like that.
обслуживают там мальчик тоже такой Так
open your mouth, please, spacers
откройте рот всё пожалуйста распорок
like that, you're lying there, you're having fun, they
такой ты себе лежишь балдеешь тебе
turned on the TV like a child, it's
телевизор включили по-детски вообще
really cool, yes, who would you like? It's better to be a dentist or a deputy, well, probably a deputy, yes,
депутатом Ну депутатом наверное да Ну
or a
или женой
deputy's wife, no, a deputy, a deputy, and how will you
депутата нет депутату депутату А как ты
become
сама станешь
a deputy yourself?  you need to or
депутатом а такого Ну тебе надо или
somehow buy a place on the list,
как-то купить место в списке
somehow have some kind of connections,
как-то иметь Ну какие-то связи как вот
just come and tell me where I’m
просто придёшь ска дате сде меня
a deputy, what do you think, this is how the
депутатом ты что думаешь это так
place works,
работает место
you’re in
стоит вы в
Novosibirsk, it’s a city with over a million people.
Новосибирске это город миллионник Да
Look, if it’s over a million people, I’m thinking about what to
смотри если миллионник я думаю что
buy where  -that’s 10,000 bucks minimum, and it’s
купить где-то 10000 баксов минимум и то
not a fact that you’ll get through to such a
не факт что пройдёте в такое
place, well, I have a smaller town there,
место нас ну у меня поменьше городок там
300,000, then here for 100 grand, we could
300.000 то тут там за 100 штук можно
buy it, but we won’t get through, it could
порешать купим но не пройдём такое может
be, and it could be because here,
быть и такое может быть потому что тут
look how you would  no one can
смотри как бы тебе же никто не может
give guarantees, but you can’t tell the
дать гарантии да ты же не скажешь потом
police later I paid for it I bought myself
в полицию Я заплатила за то Купила себе
a place and didn’t get through You Skat what’s there, well, you have to
место а не прошла Тебе Скат что там ну
think, a girl like yes, so you kind of need to
думать надо девочко типа да поэтому надо
know Well, there are all sorts of parties, there’s
как бы знать Ну есть всякие партии есть
someone out there scamming him, he says, look  there
кто-то там разводит говорит смотри тут
will be five places there, he will pass, he takes Yes, they
будет Там пять мест пройдёт берёт Да ему
give him money, in short, he takes off, he says they didn’t
бабки дают короче он снимает говорит не
pass and that’s it. That is, here you can
прошли и всё Вот то есть тут
play with this if you have a lot of
играться с этим если у тебя есть куча
money of your own, you can play around Yes, but if
своих бабок можешь поиграться Да но если
not, it’s better Don’t take risks, it’s better to find some kind of
нет лучше Не рискуй лучше Найди какой-то
Verka option and the most  It’s better to find a
Веркой варианти самое лучше найти
deputy who already has connections there,
депутата который уже имеет там связи
understands that he’ll come where and how, and he
понимает что как где прийдёт и он
can arrange a place
местечко может оформить
like, well, whatever
типа ну как
In short, you understand, grown-up girls
бы Короче вы понимаете взрослые девочки
like there are still some interesting
типа ещё есть какие-то может интересные
questions,
вопросы
I’m ready to have frank conversations today Have
Я сегодня откровенные разговоры готов
you already taken a place for someone  Well,
говорить А вы кому-то уже брали место Ну
not yet, but how would I? The fact is that
пока ещё нет но как бы я Дело в том что
when I passed I didn’t have too
когда сам прошёл у меня не было слишком
much money. I invested in my
много бабла Я себе инвестировал в своё
place. Now, after I became a
место Теперь у меня после того как стал
deputy, everything is chocolate and now
депутатом вообще всё шоколад и сейчас
I’m thinking about it. Well, I’m looking closely at the next elections.  they
вот подумаю Да что на следующие выборы
would like to be
присматриваюсь а хотели бы быть
president, that’s not it, look at the president. In short, they want
не это смотри президента Все короче от
something from him, they must koche everywhere under the
него что-то хотят должен коче всюду под
body camera of a deputy somewhere there, in short, he
теле камерой депутате где-то там короче
sewed you up, no one knows, he doesn’t see.
себе зашил тебя никто не знает не видит
In short, you decide the decision in general, like
Короче ты решаешь решение вообще типа
super And the president, look, he’s driving around
супер А президент что вот он ездит
not everyone likes to eat And you have a lot of
посмотри не все любят есть И много
ill-wishers Well, like some kind of nebro. For
недоброжелателей у вас Ну как типа небро
example, you
какие-то Вот вы например где-то там
study or work somewhere there, too, it’s just like that,
учитесь или работаете тоже так само есть
someone doesn’t like you, someone You don’t like,
кто-то вас не любит кого-то Вы не любите
this is a normal human relationship,
это нормальные человеческие отношения
everything can be resolved sat down  we
всё можно порешать сели ресторанчик
ordered a restaurant, we talked like a grater,
заказали поговорили типа тёрки
grated, it’s easier for us, like, well, the
перетёртое у нас это проще типа да ну у
deputies Well, somehow there is such a code,
депутатов Ну как-то есть такой кодекс
you know, the unspoken parliamentary one, we don’t
знаешь негласный депутатский мы не
wash dirty linen from the Security Council if we have
выносим сор из СБ если у нас есть
some kind of dirt, we talked, we discussed everything, I
какие-то дёрст поговорили обсудили Всё я
don’t interfere in your schemes, you don’t  you climb into mine
не лезу в твои схемы ты не лезешь в мои
and let’s go, yes,
и поехали да
in general, it’s super, yes, but they can order it for a
Вообще супер да а могут заказать на
deputy. Well, they can
депутата Ну могут на кого угодно могут
order it for anyone, it’s like this, it’s not like you can
заказать это ж такое тут не как бы не
hide from it. This is life, yes, for example, they can,
спрячешься от это Это жизнь да могут
for example,
например
a girl, yes, like you there, for example, promised
девушка да типа ты там например обещал
her a place like on the list Yes  that she
ей место типа в списке Да что она
will pass In short, she’s there Well, then,
пройдёт Короче она там Ну так а потом
like, you took, in short, another place VL, she
типа ты взял короче другое место ВЛ она
could have been jealous there, she took it, in short,
там могла ревнивая взяла короче было у
we had something like that and from a neighboring city, in short,
нас такое да с соседнего города короче
well, he had an affiliate program with a
ну был партнёрская программа у него
sponsorship like that, you know, like adult
спонсорская такая ну знаете типа взросло
girls, you know, and in short, he
девочки понимаете да и короче он
decided to become a sponsor for another
решил стать спонсором для другой скажем
girl, let’s say for another girl And she, in short, hired
для другого девушки И та короче наняла
Killer Yes it was Well, like they tied him up, like he
Киллера Да было Ну типа повязали типа он
got burned Killer In short, they tied him up, everything is
спалился Киллер Короче повязали всё
fine Everyone is alive,
нормально Все живы
like a
типа
woman, well,
жа ну
well, put yourself in her place, if
бы ну поставь ты себя на её место если
only you and you had a sponsorship
бы вот ты да у тебя были спонсорские
relationship  with this deputy Yes, you are about to have
отношения с этим депутатом Да ты уже
elections soon Yes you understand that he Well,
скоро выборы Да ты понимаешь что он Ну у
you have already had such a long relationship Yes that he
вас долгие уже отношения такие Да что он
will put you on the list for the checkpoint Yes and in
тебя возьмёт в список в проходное Да а
short, then he tells you like because
он короче потом тебе говорит типа потому
some new one
что какая-то На горизонте новая
has appeared on the horizon and somewhere  he decided to take her under his
появилась и где-то он решил её взять под
wing so that the truth would be evil against him too
крыло чтоб тоже на него Злая была бы
Of course, this is a man Well, what
правда Конечно это же мужчина Ну и что
would you do with him? Well, I would also
бы ты с ним сделала Ну тоже бы Киллера
order Killer, only more expensive, more expensive. And where did
заказал только подороже подороже А где у
you get money like that? I understand.
тебя бабки были такие найдётся понял
Cool, how did you get yours?
Прикольно да как у вас вы своего
you know who the deputy is in your
депутата знаете вот кто у вас там по
constituency, the deputy in Novosibirsk
округу депутат в Новосибирске
Aa No, I don’t know, but we could
Аа Нет не знаю а что могли бы
meet you here, as if
познакомиться сри вот у нас как бы вот у
you also have deputies there, that once a
вас тоже депутаты есть там что они раз в
month they have a meeting with the voter,
месяц делают встречу с избирателем там
some couple of grandmothers come there  Yes, they’re kind of
приходят какие-то пару бабушек да типа
boring, young
скучны пришли бы молоденькие такие
girls like that would come, they’re like someone someone’s on the
девушки они типа кто-то кто-то на
radar Maybe somewhere there would be a
радарах Может где-то там завязалась бы
Kato conversation, well, somehow I don’t trust
Като разговор ну я как-то не доверяю
such men. I think they
таким мужчинам Мне кажется они женщин
change women like gloves, not just for a deputy,
меняют как перчатки не как раз депутату
on the contrary, stability Because  what if you
наоборот стабильность Потому что ты если
already bought a seat? Yes, she’s been sitting with you for these
купил уже место Да она с тобой сидит эти
5 years, like in the next room, like in
5 лет типа в соседнем зале типа в
session. You can’t change us, you can’t tell us, you
сессион Нам же не поменяешь не скажешь
can’t change a deputy ska guys. I’ve
нельзя поменять депутата ска пацаны Я
changed my mind, let’s do it. Now it
короче передумал давайте Вы теперь это
won’t be for the deputies; it will be different for all the deputies
не будет депутатам другая Всё депутатам
if they’ve already decided 5 years  on the contrary,
если постановили 5 лет уже наоборот
it’s very clear, and then after 5 years he’ll
это очень чётко а потом через 5 лет он
find another Well, somehow it’s not very
другую найдётся Ну как-то не очень такое
possible, so it’s like, look
может так а так что типа вот смотри
how long it’s like this, in short, you’ve
сколько так есть короче ты дольше 5 лет
been dating some guy for longer than 5 years. No, well, that’s
встречалась с пацаном каким-то Нет ну
what, but at least here  5 years There is a
вот что а тут уже хотя бы 5 лет Есть
guarantee And so, like, you know they
гарантия А так типа что знаешь у них
all have the wind in their heads, he walked for six months,
всех Ветер в голове он погулял полгода
then in short, he forgot, in short, this is all a
потом короче забил забыл короче это всё
normal topic, so, well, adults,
нормальная тема такая ну то взрослые вам
how
по сколько
old are we? We are 20 to 20. Well, I
лет нам по 20 по 20 Ну вот мне уже 42
’ll be 42 soon, like, I  as if I’ve seen
будет скоро типа то я как бы повидал
such things you know So what is 5
такие знаешь вещи Так что Что такое 5
years 5 years is generally a Mega
лет 5 лет это вообще Мега
term and what do you have to do with your wife Yes yes I have a
срок а вы жена причём Да да у меня есть
ring uh The thing is that in the parliamentary
кольцо ээ Дело в том что в депутатской
sphere if you get even 5 years on the
сфере ты если попадёшь даже на 5 лет в
Council you will already get to know each other  you will be
Совет ты познакомишься уже ты уже будешь
in the circle of deputies, so different, yes, that is,
в кругу депутатов так других да то есть
some officials of some kind,
какие-то чиновники какие-то там
prosecutors, this is already a grater, this is already completely
Прокуроры это уже тёрки это уже совсем
different, you will already be steaming with all the others in
другой ты уже будешь со всеми другими
short thoughts, so you will not
париться короче мыслями Так ты не будешь
think about how to get up for work in the morning,
думать как короче утром встать на работу
you are thinking [ __ ], what is today  in short,
ты думаешь Бля что сегодня короче В
which restaurant should I go to to eat? That’s
какой ресторан пойти покушать Вот это
the problem. It’s like that because
самая проблема Типа так потому что типа
you go to the same restaurant for 3 days in a row, and
ты 3 дня подряд вот если ходишь в один и
your colleagues and deputies
тот же ресторан тебя коллеги депутаты
say that you go to the
говорят что типа ну что ты ходишь в один
same restaurant like damn. Well, that’s
и тот же ресторан типа блин Ну это
some-  you know, that is, you need to change
какая-то типа знаешь то есть надо менять
restaurants like that Well, like And then this
рестораны так Ну типа А то одно это
very menu is some kind of [ __ ] yeah Uh-huh
самое меню ка фигня какая-то да Угу
Yes and your wife is also in this business
Да а а ваша жена тоже в этом бизнесе
or in some other field in
крутится или в какой-то другой сфере в
another field in another she’s kind of outside
другой сфере в другой она как бы вне
she’s not
политики она политикой не
interested in politics, well, that’s
интересуется ну как бы это
good, well,
хорошо Ну да
yes, she was interested, well, like, politics
интересовалась Да ну типа ж политика
is such a topic, yes, you
такая тема да вы
understand, well, yes,
понимаете Ну да
yes. Have you ever thought about going to some
да А вы не думали там поехать в какую-то
other country to live there? Have you
другую страну жить
thought about some other Well,
думали в какую-нибудь другую Ну только
not Well, Israel  Israel, do you have
не Ну Израиль Израиль а у вас есть
some kind of Jewish roots to go to Israel?
какие-то корни еврейские чтобы в Израиль
Well, I like the contingents and in
уехать Ну мне нравятся контингенты и
general I understand the
вообще Поня
traditions. What about Novosibirsk? It’s cold and
традиции А что в Новосибирске Холодно и
somehow boring, the boys are drinking. Yes,
как-то скучно пацаны бухают Да да
yes, that is, finding a normal guy in Novosibirsk
да то есть в новосиби найти нормального
is a problem, I understand that  I didn’t
мужика это проблемка я так Поня чтобы не
drink, like, well, and
бухал типа ну и так
worked like that, well, I don’t know, I don’t like Russians at all
работал ну не знаю мне вообще русские не
and they’re generally just ordinary guys, so
нравятся и вообще обычны парни а
what? Well, because they have such an attitude towards women. Whatever I’m not really well aware of. Well, I don’t know. Well, how about things or something? Well, that’s how  things
Ну как к вещи что ли Ну вот как вещи Ну
Well, what like she you whom if he is
а что типа она тебя кого если он с тобой
dating you he believes that you are his
встречается он считает что ты это его
property yes Well yes there is such a type he
собственность да Ну да есть такое типа
doesn’t respect your inner world no No I’m
не уважает твой внутренний мир не Нет я
not talking about that I mean that there is no
не про это я имею в виду что нету вот
such thing
этого
as respect for the post
как уважения поста
Well  how does this manifest itself, that he
Ну а как В чём это проявляется он что
hits there, swears at a woman, I don’t know,
бьёт там матюкается на женщину я не знаю
I only met a Russian
я встречалась один раз только с русским
guy once, and what kind of guys have you
парнем а с какими ты парнями
met? I don’t live in Russia at all, but
встречалась я вообще не живу в России а
where are you, that is, are you in Novosibirsk now
где ты то есть ты в Новосибирске сейчас
or where am I just coming here?  Cool
или где я просто приезжаю сюда Прикольно
And where are you from?
А откуда ты
Dubai is you coming to Dubai,
Дубай это ты в Дубай приезжаешь
no I live in Dubai, I come here to
нет Я живу в Дубае я приезжаю сюда в
Russia with
Россию
my relatives and friends, and in Dubai you
сво родственников и друзей а в Дубае ты
obviously don’t work as a dentist. As I
явно не стоматологом работаешь Я так
understand it, I’m not working yet, I’m studying. Well, I
понимаю я пока не работаю учусь Ну всё я
understand everything, you’re not a dentist in  Are you
понял ты не на стоматолога в Дубае
studying in Dubai Why are you studying to be a dentist? Yes, in
учишься Почему на стоматолога Да в
Dubai, you think
Дубае вы думаете
I’m
я что
Lil, this is the first time I’ve heard that I’m a
Лиль я впервые слы что
dentist, I live there because
стоматолога я там живу потому что там
my parents live there. Your parents, where do
мои родители живут Ваши родители где
my parents live? My mother and my boyfriend
живут мои родители Моя мама и мой очем
live in Dubai. But I don’t understand them very well. Not
живут в Дубае А понял они не очень Не
Russian.  yes very No not Russian at all
русский да очень Нет не русский всё
That’s why you don’t like Russians yes yes we don’t
Поэтому русских и не любите да да не
like you and your second girlfriend is from Novosibirsk
любим а вторая подружка вы с новосиба
or also from Dubai No I live here I understand that
или тоже с Дубая Нет я тут живу понял то
means you are less lucky in Sochi yes
есть вам Сочи вам меньше повезло
So yes I understand well Maybe there
да Так что есть понял хорошо Может ещё
are some other questions  I do
какие-то вопросики есть
n’t even know the deputy ones, well, you wo
депутатские не знаю даже ну вы в Дубае
n’t be lost in Dubai. Yes, you from Novosibirsk
се не пропадёт Да вот вам из новосиба
need to somehow move somewhere along the
надо как-то где-то двигаться по
deputy lines,
депутатский линиям
somehow we’ll put her in a deputy.
каким-то депутат её
I think she’s cute, she can
поставим Я думаю она симпатично может
find herself a deputy, you’ll find
найти себе депутата найдёте
deputies. Why
депутати Почему именно
can a deputy be a deputy?
депутат может и депутат
if you have people
это если есть у вас
like that, that all the deputies with
такие что все депутаты с
a belly, not all of them, at first you come in like a
пузиком не все сначала ты входишь типа
normal prek, then you sit and
нормальный прек да Потом сидишь сидишь и
in short, you start to get fat,
короче уже типа начинаешь жирнеть
get fat, there are those who have been there for three
жирнеть есть такие которые там по три
convocations, they generally can barely get through the doors,
созыва были они вообще там еле в двери
consider that now this is your country  is
относите что сейчас вот ваша страна
fighting against Ukraine negative negative
воюет против Украины негативно негативно
Ponya Yes, this is at least good So
Поня Да это хоть хорошо Так что есть у
you have a chance to find yourself a
вас шанс найти себе
deputies A bright soul loves this Yes,
депутати Светлая душа такое любят Да
okay, let's run That's all Let's
хорошо ладно давайте побегу Всё Давайте
flask subscribe to my Telegram right
опоки подпишись на мий Telegram прям
now the axis of wine and
зараз ось вин а
bye as much and as much respectful as possible YouTube keeping us busy
пок дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня нас
through skarg  or in your ban and a lot more
через скарг ор в твый бан и дуже багато
videos I don’t show people at all times don’t show
видео не показую людям вчасно не показуе
information about streams for this purpose for
информация про стримы тому для того щоб
Mali to write an operational link
ми Мали оперативный звязок пишиться
right away and Popik there in telegra okm
прямо зараз а Попик там в телегра окм
video sche tezh Tsikava and Korisna information
видео ще теж цикава и корисна информация
and we will blame you on Trima postiyny
и мы повинни з вами трима постийний
operational link
оперативный звязок
Nezalezhno in that chi show you about it
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про це
YouTube Glory to Ukraine subscribe
YouTube Слава Украине подпишись